鉄で出来た凹凸の街で
In this rugged iron city,
ずっと見慣れた夢も　枯れそう
the dreams I'm used to seeing always wither.
交差点はこもれ陽で揺らいだ
Wavering amidst the sifted sunlight,
途方にくれて見失う道
I become lost at an intersection.
サヨナラをたくさん思い出して
Suddenly I remember all the goodbyes
ふいに浮かぶメロディー
and I am flooded with memories.
とても輝いて見える空を
The shining sky glistens
錆びたブランコこいで仰ぐ
from where I gaze on this rusted swing.
流れてく雲はなんか叙情的
I always stare at the blue cracks
隙間の青をずっと眺めた
peaking between the story-telling clouds
舞いあがって思いも投げたら
If I could throw my feelings into the air,
憂い消えた
my sadness would fade
風が変わって　冷たい季節の予感で
The change in wind is the beginning of a cold season
グルグル回る　切ない心飛ばされて
My wounded heart flies in circles
漂いながら　君にまで届けばいいな
I wish it could reach you as it floats
僕だけの花　季節はずれた咲いたらいいな
Only my flower blooms out of season
未来まで透けるような、寒い空ーー。
The cold sky shows through to the future--.
言葉つむいで作る希望
My hopes and words are stitched together
明日を手さぐりでまた探す
I search and fumble my way into tomorrow
色つけずに世界を描いた
I paint a world
君を描く絵の具だけ残してさ
where only you have color
出来たらすぐ見せに行かなくちゃ
I have to show you as soon as I can
褪せる前に
before it fades
風が変わって　冷たい季節の匂いで
The change in wind smells like a cold season
キラキラしてる　素直な心気づいたよ
My wounded heart glitters in pain
ただ揺れながら　君の前で笑ってたいな
I want to smile with you even though I tremble
名前のない花　季節はずれた咲いたらいいな
Only the flower with no names bloom out of season
未来まで透けるような、寒い空ーー。
The cold sky shows through to the future--.
風が変わって　冷たい季節の予感で
The change in wind is the beginning of a cold season
グルグル回る　切ない心飛ばされて
My wounded heart flies in circles
漂いながら　君にまで届けばいいな
I wish it could reach you as it floats
僕だけの花　季節はずれた咲いたらいいな
Only my flower blooms out of season
ただ揺れながら　君の前で笑ってたいな
I want to smile with you even though I tremble
名前のない花　季節はずれた咲いたらいいな
Only the flower with no names bloom out of season
未来まで透けるような、寒い空ーー。
The cold sky shows through to the future--.